Company Benefits Summary Plan Description /4060
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Company Benefits Summary Plan Description
1976-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mitchell, Olivia
/4060
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7980436
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 07, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5003: U.S. President's Railroad Commission Records 5009mf: United Steelworkers of America, Local 2601 Minute Books and Roster Book on Microfilm 5024: Theodore W. Kheel Arbitration Awards 5040: U.S. Emergency Board No. 106 Records 5043: U.S. Emergency Board No. 114 Records 5044: U.S. Emergency Board No. 116 Reports and Exhibits 5053: U.S. Emergency Board No. 130 Records 5054: U.S. Emergency Board No. 133 Exhibits 5070: American Smelting and Refining Co. and the United Steelworkers of America Hearing before the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board Transcript and Exhibits 5074: U.S. Board of Inquiry on the 1959 Labor Dispute in the Steel Industry Records 5075: U.S. Emergency Board under the Taft Hartley Act Records 5118: New York City Board of Transportation and the Transport Workers Union Records 5149: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5206: Local 1199 Records 5216: Theresa Wolfson Papers 5231: Arthur S. Meyer Papers 5250: William Goff Caples Speeches 5258: William Standard Papers 5298: IAM vs. Northwest Airlines and Miscellaneous others Arbitration Proceedings 5301mf: United Mine Workers of America District 12 (Ill.) Records on Microfilm 5305: Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5328: Ralph T. Seward Papers 5493: Elmer E. Hilpert Arbitration Papers 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5533: Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Company Records 5538: James C. Hill Arbitration Files 5548: I. Robert Feinberg Arbitration Records 5588: David L. Cole Papers 5602: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5680oh: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5780-154: ILGWU President's Office Records 5782: Olivia Mitchell Collection of Health and Welfare Plans' Descriptions 5839: Vernon Jenson Additional Arbitration Files 6047: Archives Information File 6291: New York State Department of Labor Benefits Files
Employee fringe benefits; Mitchell, Olivia.
7980436
- ABT Associates Inc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ARO Inc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Able Steel Rule, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Adams Rite Industries Inc., 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Aerofin Corporation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agriculture Services Inc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Allergy Consultants P.C., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alley, S.A. MD PC, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Allied Maintenance Corporation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Allied Metals Company, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Aloha Airlines Inc., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Allyn and Bacon, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Alta Industries Corporation (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Transit Union (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Agar and Chemical Company, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- American Airlines Inc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Lung Association of Eastern Missouri, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- American Can Company, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- American Hospital Supply (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American National Insurance Company, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American National Red Cross (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American State Bank, Lubbock TX., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Andrecom Advisors Corporation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Appleyard Motor Transportation Company (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Architectonics Inc. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Arkansas Cement Corp., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Armco Steel Corporation, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Arnot, Henry E. DDS (Box 1, Folder 28)
- The Ashland Bank and Savings Company, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Askew, Wilson and Dicicco P.A. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Atlantic Bank of New York, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Automotive Supply Company (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Babcock & Wilson Paris Works, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Baker Fentress & Company (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Baltimore, The Saving Bank of (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bambergers (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bankers Trust New York Corporation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Barker Jenning Corporation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bateman, Eicher, Hill Richards, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Baxter Travenol Laboratories, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Baxter Travenol Laboratories, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Belden Corporation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Benjamin Electrical Engineering (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Best Foods Employees Association Inc. (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Betz Laboratories Inc. (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Blum & Rizzo P.C., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- The Boeing Company, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- The Boomer Co., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Bournival/ Chrysler- Plymouth, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- The Bowery Savings Bank (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Boy Scouts of America (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Brex & Vandersnow Inc. (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Brockton Orthopedic Associates Inc., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Broer Grocery Company (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Brown Palace Hotel, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Buchanan Metalform Products Inc., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Buhrman- Pharr Hardware Company, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Building Service Employees, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bux-Mont Podiatry Associates Inc., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Byron Road Medical Group P.C., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- CTS Corporation Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cadillac Rubber & Plastic Inc. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Caldwell's Windowcare Inc. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Markevich, John N, DDS (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Petersen, Wilbert I., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Itokazu, Harold M.D., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Barusch, Leo M.D. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Osumi, Jerry Y. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Phillips, Lawrence MD, DDS, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Arima, Kazuo, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Giachetti, Ernest G. DDS, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cottrell, John Kevin M.D., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Aubell, Robert J. M.D. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Dierkes, Donald D. DDS., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Elberg, Robert M., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The Carborundum Company, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cargill Inc. & Associates Co., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Carl- Lac Electronic Industrial Sales Inc., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- G.O. Carlson, Inc., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Carmi, Marcel D, DDS, PC, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Carpenters Pension Trust Fund of St. Louis, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Carter Hawley Hale Stores, Inc., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Castoldi, Thomas A. M.D. and Associates (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Cedar Rapids Lumber Co. Inc. (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Cedar Rapids Radiologist, PC, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- CertainTeed, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Chase Manhattan Bank, NA (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Children's Aid Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Christianson Furniture Corporation, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Chrysler Corporation, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Citizens National Bank & Trust Co., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Clark Equipment Co., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Clark's Finer Food. Inc., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Clark Furniture Inc. (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Bank of Clearwater, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Clearwater Laundry & Cleaners Inc., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Cole Laboratories- Canada, Ltd., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Cole, Steve A. CPA, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- College Stores, National Association of, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Colonial Mortgage Service Company (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Colorado Springs Neurological Association, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Colvert Dairy Products Company, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Combustion Engineering Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Comco Productions Inc. (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Community Radiology Associates P.A., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Computer System Architects, Inc., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Consolidated Edison Company of New York, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Consumers Power Company, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Crane & Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Crane Smith Dermatologic P.A. (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Crenshaw, Ware & Johnson, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Crutcher Resources Corporation, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Culbert Construction Company, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Cummings Engines of Tennessee, Inc., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- D'Andrea Electric Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Dana Corporation (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Danners Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Dart Industries Inc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Decatur County Bank (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Diamond Shamrock Corporation (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Diamond- Sunsweet, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Dixie Construction Company Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Dixie Furniture Company Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Drew, Duffy & Leyhane (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Dunter Corporation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Duriron Company Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- ESB Incorporated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Eagle Cornice Company Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- East Federal Savings & Loan, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- East River Management Corp., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Eastman Kodak, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Eberhard Foods, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Eggers Hardwood Products Corp., 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Ehikian, Richard G. DDS (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Electro-Nucleonics, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Eli Lilly & Company, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Elk Air Conditioning Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Envirotech Corporation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Eric Salm, Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Essex Radiological Associates Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Everett Clinic Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Exchange Building Corporation (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Falls Cities Carpenters (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Farm Bureau Services (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Farmers National Bank (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Farmers Union Central Exchange Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Federal Paper Board, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Field Communications Corporation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- First Holding Company Inc. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- First National Bank of Sweetwater, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- First National Holding Corporation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Fisher, Wayland, Southwayd & Cooper (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Fishers Control Company, Continental Division, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Fleetwood Enterprises Inc. (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Fletcher's Inc., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Floor Covering Enterprises Inc., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Florida Commercial Bank, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Foldcraft Co., 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Ford Motor Company, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Forms Plus, Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Foster Grant Co. (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Fred Hunter Funeral Homes Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Freeman, W.H. & Company, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Freight Drivers Local 557, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- C.L. Frost & Son Inc. (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Fullerton Tire & Supply Co., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Gate City Savings & Loan Association (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Gateway Corporation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- General Battery Corporation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- General Bridgeville Division, Ionics, Inc., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- General Foods Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- George Amstey Ob-Gyn Inc. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- George B.H. Macomber Company, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- George J. Howe Company Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- George F. Schuler, Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- George W. Dahl Company, Inc., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Gerald's Studio & Camera Shop Inc., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Gilbert Robinson Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Godchaux- Henderson Sugar Co, Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Goldenberg, Irwin DDS & David Weil DDS, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Goldsborough, Thompson & Bizot, Drs. (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Goodman Bensman Funeral Home, Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Goodman, Herbert W. DDS. P.C., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Goody's Manufacturing Corporation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Gould General Coverage Inc. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. Inc. (A&P Stores), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Green Bay Broadcasting Company (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Griggs, William C. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- The Guardian Life Insurance Co., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- H.H. Robertson Company, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Hailey Transportation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Hallett Pontiac Inc. (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Hallmark Cards Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Hammermill Paper Company, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Hancock Grain Company, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Hansen Fruit & Cold Storage Co. (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Hardy Salt Company, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Harris Trust & Savings Bank of Chicago, Ill. (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Harry Grodsky & Company, Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Heeren Co. (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Heights Finance Corp. (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Herndon, Roy L., MD Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Herold Publishing Company (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Hitchiner Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Hodgson, Russ, Andrews Woods & Goodyear (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Holiday Inns Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Hoosier Gas Company (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Horsman Dolls Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Howard Decorative Packaging Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Hub Clothiers (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Huck Manufacturing Company, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Illinois Bell (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Interpace Corporation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- J.C. Penney Co. Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- J. Grady Randolf, Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- J.J. Case (Box 4, Folder 50)
- J.J. Keller & Associates Inc., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- J.K. Boersma Beverage Co. Inc. (Box 4, Folder 52)
- J.M. Huber Corporation (Box 4, Folder 53)
- James & Lidstone M.D. P.A., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Jays Food Inc. (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Jewel Companies Inc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Jiffy Manufacturing Company (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Jim Farley & Son Inc. (Box 4, Folder 58)
- John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Johns Manville Corporation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Jolo Corporation (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Julius Rothschild & Company, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kane- Miller Corporation (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Kane- Miller Corporation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Kane- Miller Corporation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Kane- Miller Corporation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Kane- Miller Corporation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Kane- Miller Corporation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Key Banks, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kingston Animal Hospital Inc. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Kitsap Physicians Service, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Knechtel Auto Service Inc. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Kores, Ambrose B. M.D. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Krahmer & Krahmer (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Krause, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Leach Company, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Leeds & Northrup Company (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Lennox Industries Inc., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Levi Strauss & Company (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Liberty Bank, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Liberty Furniture Company, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Liberty Mutual Life Insurance Corp., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Lipman, Antonelli, Batt & Dunlop, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Lloyd Noland Foundation Inc., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- London Parking, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Long Beach School Employees Federal Credit Union, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Look & Morison Architects (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Loveland Savings & Loan Association, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Low, Roy D. D.D.S. Inc. (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Lundberg Screw Products Company, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Lyon Inc., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- MCC Pacific Southern Foundries, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Mac- Vicar- Wells, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mac's General Merchandise, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Macon Janitor Service Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Macy, R.H. & Co. Inc. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Macy's California (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Magaziner, Martin D.D.S. P.A., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Mainzer, Sheft, Benzian & Annes MD's (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Malark, Mary Ann, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Mallinckrodt Inc., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Malone, James P., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Manitowoc Company Inc., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Manual Arts Furniture Co. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Maola Milk & Ice Cream Co., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Marathon Oil Company, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Marquiss, Lorence B., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Marshburn, Shuford, Smith & Snyder (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Mason & Hanger- Silas Mason Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Maverick Markets Inc., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- McCorkle Construction Co., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- McDonnell Douglas Corporation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- McDougall, W.J., M.D. (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Mead Corporation (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Meakons McKinnon, Inc., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Meat Cutters Local 539, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Metalock Corporation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Metropolitan Edison Co., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Miguel Figuerda MD & Associates, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Milwaukee Die Casting Company, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Missouri, Portland Cement Company, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Mobile Oil Corp. (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Monarch Tool & Gauge Company (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Morbark Industries Inc. (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Morison & McCallie P.A. (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Mosinee Paper Corporation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Mott's Super Market, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Muffler Shops of St. Petersburg Inc. (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Mutual Insurers Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- NB Corporation (Box 6, Folder 39)
- NCR Corporation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- N & W Sales Inc. (Box 6, Folder 41)
- NECA - IBEW Local 700, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- National Association of Industrial Trade Unions, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- National Conveyers Company Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- National Forge Company, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- National Wooden Pallet and Container Association, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- New American Library Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- New England Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Box 6, Folder 48)
- New York Backstretch Employees, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Newark Beth Israel Medical Center, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Newman- Crosby Steel Inc., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Niagara Falls (Box 6, Folder 52)
- North Carolina Savings & Loan League, Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Northeastern Savings & Loan Association, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Northern Chesapeake Builders Corp., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Northern States Power Co.- Minnesota, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Northwestern Steel & Wire Company, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Northwestern Supply Company, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Oakite Products, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Ohio National Life Insurance Co., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Ohio Operating Engineers (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Olin Corporation (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Olney Oil & Burner Company Inc. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Oneida National Bank & Trust (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Oppegard Equipment Company (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Orthopaedics- Indianapolis, Inc., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Overhead Door Company of Watertown, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Oxford Savings Bank, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- PPG Industries, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Pacific Supply Cooperative (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Parks, R.M. Inc., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Parr Lumber Co. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Patterson Oil Co. Inc. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Pease Company, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Pease Machine & Tool, Inc., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Manufacturers Association (Box 8, Folder 8)
- People's Bank & Trust Co. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Perrott Associates, Inc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Pesin, Sydney, Bernard Advertising, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Peter Pan World Travel Inc., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Peterson, Lavin F. D.D.S. Ltd. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Petrouits & Tepper Inc. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Pfizer, Inc., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Phoenix Steel Corporation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Pic & Pay Stores, Inc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Piedmont Mill Supply Company, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Piedmont Natural Gas Company, Inc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Lager Beer Brewers Association Union, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Platt, David M.D. & Associates, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Portland Electric & Plumbing Co. (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Potlatch Corporation (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Power & Telephone Supply Company, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Prairie State Screw & Bolt Corp., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Presbyterian Day School, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Pressman's Publishers, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Prime Tanning Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Printing Industry Pension Plan, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Producer- Wrier Guild of America, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Professional Radiology Associates, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Profit Sharing Council of America, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Progressive Dietary Consultants, Inc., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- QSP, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Quadrastat Controls Corp. (Box 8, Folder 35)
- RCA Corporation (Box 8, Folder 36)
- R.K. Black, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Radha R. Baishnat M.D. F.R.C.P. Inc. (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Raleigh Lithograph Corp. (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Rapid City Regional Hospital Inc. (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Drs. Rattan & Barnes, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- G. Findlay Reed, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Rhode Island Carpenters Pension Plan, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Richardson, Keister L D.D.S. P.A., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Ripple & Chambers, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Robert E. Nelson Associates Inc. (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Rock Island Refining Corp., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Rocky Mountain Machinery Co., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Roland Wilbert Vault Co. Inc., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Royal Industries Inc., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Ruggerio, Anthony C. D.D.S. (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Sacherman, Robert H. M.D. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- St. Elizabeth Hospital Medical Center, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Scenic Artists, United Local 829, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Schwantes, J.H. D.D.S. P.A., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Scott Paper Company, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Scudder, Stevens & Clark (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Security Finance Corporation (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Sharon Steel Corporation, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Shelby Memorial Hospital (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Shuman, Martin J. M.D. P.A. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Sikeston Publishing Company, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Silver Spring Auto City, Inc., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Skaggo- Walsh, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Smith Companies, Charles E., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Smithkline Corp- Smithkline & French, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Somerville Associates, John E. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- South Carolina Electric & Gas Co., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- South Norwalk Plant UPO Inc. (Box 9, Folder 18)
- South Texas Retina Consultants P.A. (Box 9, Folder 19)